Welcome to Manulife Vitality Stories!
Once upon a time, Ed wondered how he could earn Vitality Points™.
The first chapter in Ed’s story was to find out what they are.
It’s simple: You can earn Vitality Points through healthy activities. And those points can turn into valuable rewards.
What are those rewards?
That’s what Ed found out in Chapter 2!
If you reach your weekly points target through steps or workouts,
you can spin the Vitality Wheel for a chance to earn gift cards from popular brands.
But you can earn even more rewards by improving your Vitality Status.
And that led Ed smoothly into Chapter 3!
Status works a little differently for the two Manulife Vitality options.
You can have Vitality Go at no cost with your insurance policy,
which gives you valuable discounts and you can earn Vitality Wheel spins with your points.
But Ed is a Vitality Plus member.
For a few bucks a month, that means points earn spins, but also add up to more rewards when he increases his Vitality Status!
Rise to Silver Status and save on insurance,
and increase your discounts on many popular brands!
And all those savings increase even more as you rise to Gold and Platinum Status.
But now Ed was thinking: “This is amazing, but how do I get these points?”
So he cracked open Chapter 4!
Manulife Vitality isn’t just about workouts and steps.
There are so many ways to earn Vitality Points.
Just look at them all!
By the way, here’s a hot tip:
make sure to open the app at least once a week, so you don’t miss out on syncing your points.
Those points will be ready for you within 48 hours of earning them.
And in case you and Ed were still wondering about those steps and workouts,
you can earn up to 40 points per day for those!
All that can add up to 18,000 points per year!
Ed knew that meant he’d live happily ever after,
with piles of points and rewards! Hopefully you can, too!
Want to check out more Manulife Vitality “how-to” stories?
Click on one of the other videos you see here, then you could live happily ever after!